Scheinman, Martin Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6287
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin Scheinman Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements
1943-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Scheinman, Martin
6287
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
6580297
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619/001: ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5663 mf: Collective Bargaining Agreements on Microfilm 5780/075: ILGWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5780/075 mf: ILGWU Collective Bargaining Agreements on Microfilm 5780/202: ILGWU Operations Department Collective Bargaining Agreements 6030: Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6065: PERB Collective Bargaining Agreements from States other than New York 6124: Collective Bargaining Agreements for New York State Employees 6178: BLS/OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6193: Communications Workers of America Collective Bargaining Agreements 6297: Peter A. Gold Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements
Collective labor agreements; Municipal officials and employees -- Labor unions; Service industries workers -- Labor unions; Postal service -- Employees -- Labor unions; Construction industry -- Employees -- Labor unions; Telecommunication -- Employees -- Labor unions; Engineers -- Labor unions; Nurses -- Labor unions; Electricians -- Labor unions; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions; Criminal justice personnel -- Labor unions; Suffolk County (N.Y.); Westchester County (N.Y.); AFSCME; Airborne Freight Corporation; American Arbitration Association; American Postal Workers Union; Building and Construction Trades Council of Greater New York; Civil Service Employees Association (N.Y.); Communications Workers of America; Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc.; Continental Airlines; Federation of Nurses and Health Professionals, AFT, AFL-CIO; Group Health Incorporated; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers-Communications Workers of America; International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers-Communications Workers of America. Local 444; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Lockheed Martin; Long Island Lighting Company; Long Island Rail Road.; Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company; Lutheran Medical Center (New York, N.Y.); National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians; National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.); National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug & Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.); National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug & Hospital Union (Connecticut); New York (State). Dept. of Correctional Services; New York State Police; New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO; New York/New Jersey General Trucking; Office and Professional Employees International Union. Local 153 (New York, N.Y.); Police Benevolent Association of the New York State Troopers; Port Authority of New York and New Jersey; Rutgers University; Service Employees International Union; Service Employees International Union. Local 200; Suffolk County (N.Y.). Association of Municipal Employees; Suffolk County (N.Y.). Detectives Association; Suffolk County Water Authority; Unisys Corporation; United States Postal Service; Vassar College; Verizon --New Jersey; Westchester County (N.Y.). Corrections Superior Officers Association
6580297
- 1199 SEIU/Greater New York Health Care Facilities Association, 1997-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Arbitration Association. Seventy-Five Years of Service, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME)/Rutgers University, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Law Enforcement Officers/State of New York, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- American Postal Workers Union, National Association of Letter Carriers/United States Postal Service, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Building and Construction Trades Council/Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Civil Service Employees Asscociation (CSEA)/Nassau County, 1990-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Civil Service Employees Asscociation (CSEA)/State of New York, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Civil Service Employees Asscociation (CSEA)/Orange County, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Civil Service Employees Asscociation (CSEA)/Town of Hempstead, NY, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Communication Workers of America (CWEA)/Associated Press, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Communication Workers of America (CWEA)/Verizon of New Jersey, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- District 1199/State of Connecticut, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Engineers Union, Local 444/Lockheed Martin, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Fedration of Nurses/Lutheran Medical Center, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Long Island Lighting Company, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers/Lockheed Martin, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers/Unisys, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Long Island Railroad (LIRR) Police Benevolent Association/Long Island Railroad (LIRR), 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1943-1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET)/ABC, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- New York State Correctional Officers/State of New York, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union/GHI, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Public Employees Federation/State of New York, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- SEIU Local 200United/Vassar College, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- State Troopers NCO Association of New Jersey/State of New Jersey, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Suffolk County Association of Municipal Employees/Suffolk County, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Suffolk County Detectives Association/Suffolk County, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Teachers, 1989-2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Teamsters/Airborne Freight, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Teamsters/Continental Airlines, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Teamsters/New Jersey-New York General Trucking, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- UAW, Legal Services Staff Association/Legal Services for New York City, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Utility Workers' Union/Consolidated Edison, 1996-2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Utility Workers' Union/Suffolk County Water Authority, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Westchester County Corrections Superior Officers Association/Westchester County, 1996-2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)